(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T21:35:44.245882",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ロマンティック
Romantic,
恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
the festive mode where flowers of love bloom!
史上最大の恋が始まりそう
The greatest love in history is about to begin.
毎日見かける あの人に
With that person I see every day,
恋してたの
I fell in love...
毎日見かける あの人に
With that person I see every day,
恋し…
I fell in...
ロマンティック
Romantic
恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Festive mode where flowers of love bloom
史上最大の恋が始まりそう
The greatest love in history is about to begin
毎日見かけるあの人に恋してた
I fell in love with that person I see every day
普段は仲間としゃがんでいる
He's usually hanging out with his friends
目立つ人
He stands out
自転車置き場の前 油断していたなら
Unprepared, right in front of the bike stand
急に彼が携帯番号 メモにしてくれた
Suddenly he wrote down his phone number on a memo
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 地元の駅
Romantic, local station where flowers of love bloom
いつもと違う景色に変わった
The usual scenery has changed
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Romantic, festive mode where flowers of love bloom
悟られないように メモを受け取った
So he wouldn't notice, I took the memo
お家に着くまでメモは見ずに一目散
I ran straight home without looking at the memo
それでも半信半疑だし変な気分
Still, I felt a bit doubtful and strange
"夜の9時になったら電話が欲しい" と
"I want a call at 9 PM,"
きっちり時間書いてあった そこにグッとこない？
The exact time was written there. Doesn't that get to you?
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
気になるドラマの始まる気配だわ
It's when my favorite drama is about to start
ロマンティック 恋の花には勇気がいる
Romantic, the flower of love takes courage
部屋に鍵かけて 時計とにらめっこ
Locking my room, I stare down the clock
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
史上最大ね心の big parade
The greatest big parade of the heart in history
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 私の部屋
Romantic, my room blooming with flowers of love
いつもと違う景色に変わった
The usual scenery has changed
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Romantic, festive mode where flowers of love bloom
悟られないように 恋が始まりそう
So he wouldn't notice, love is about to begin
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 地元の駅
Romantic, local station where flowers of love bloom
いつもと違う景色に変わった
The usual scenery has changed
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Romantic, festive mode where flowers of love bloom
悟られないように メモを受け取った
So he wouldn't notice, I took the memo
お家に着くまでメモは見ずに一目散
I ran straight home without looking at the memo
それでも半信半疑だし変な気分
Still, I felt a bit doubtful and strange
"夜の9時になったら電話が欲しい" と
"I want a call at 9 PM,"
きっちり時間書いてあった そこにグッとこない？
The exact time was written there. Doesn't that get to you?
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
気になるドラマの始まる気配だわ
It's when my favorite drama is about to start
ロマンティック 恋の花には勇気がいる
Romantic, the flower of love takes courage
部屋に鍵かけて 時計とにらめっこ
Locking my room, I stare down the clock
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
史上最大ね心の big parade
The greatest big parade of the heart in history
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 私の部屋
Romantic, my room blooming with flowers of love
いつもと違う景色に変わった
The usual scenery has changed
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Romantic, festive mode where flowers of love bloom
悟られないように 恋が始まりそう
So he wouldn't notice, love is about to begin
汐留みたいな心の big parade
The big parade of the heart like Shiodome
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 私の部屋
Romantic, my room blooming with flowers of love
いつもと違う景色に変わった
The usual scenery has changed
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 浮かれモード
Romantic, festive mode where flowers of love bloom
悟られないように 恋が始まりそう
So he wouldn't notice, love is about to begin
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
気になるドラマの始まる気配だわ
It's when my favorite drama is about to start
ロマンティック 恋の花には勇気がいる
Romantic, the flower of love takes courage
部屋に鍵かけて 時計とにらめっこ
Locking my room, I stare down the clock
ロマンティック 恋の花咲く 夜の9時は
Romantic, at 9 PM when flowers of love bloom,
史上最大ね心の big parade
The greatest big parade of the heart in history
Yeah, Kikiriki! Woohoo! Did you enjoy that?
Hello everybody, welcome! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth, and I welcome you to my very special Holoproduction cover song, Kiara and Friends Spring Concert!
Hello everybody, welcome! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth, and I welcome you to my very special Holoproduction cover song, Kiara & Friends Spring Concert!
Woohoo! Yes, it is Holoproduction's dream. Do you know what Holoproduction is?
I used to go to so many Holoproduction concerts back in the day. I love Holoproduction, it's an idol agency that has several different groups like Monimusu and Berryz Kobo and C-ute and so many more!
I used to go to so many Holoproduction concerts back in the day. I love Holoproduction, it's an idol agency that has several different groups like Morning Musume, Berryz Kobo, C-ute, and so many more!
So today, I will introduce all of them to you, yeah! And don't forget to use the hashtag #HPmeetsHoloEN so that I can look at your screenshots and everybody gets to know even if they missed the live stream.
You can maybe tell them to watch the vod. Yay, yay, yay! And so I kicked things off with the legendary "Romantic Ukare Mode" by Fujimoto Miki-san.
Who is—she wrote history! You don't even understand! She's a Holoproduction idol legend!
So I hope that came across a little bit. Of course, I'm not on her level, but you know, you know.
Okay, so besides performing many, many, many Holoproduction songs, we'll also be having as many Hololive English members...
invited here today as possible,
And that might even mean
that we get a member who you haven't seen in a long, long time!
You already know, don't you? Mhm!
Yes! And also, we have flower crowns, as you can maybe tell. Pretty, pretty. Well,
we have these yellow ones, but who knows, maybe we'll have some other colors too, because Hello Project also means many different colors, image colors,
and personalities, and we're going to show them with these flowers.
And one more thing, the stage! Let's give an applause for the stage! Woohoo, the stage! Thank you for coming, you cute little toodies!
Are you excited for a big concert out here in this outdoor square?
Yay yay yay yay!
All right! Then let's jump right into it! Everybody, let's have a great time! Enjoy! Woo!
アメちゃん！来てくれたの！？ありがとう！
Amelia! You're here too?! Thank you!
ガチンコで行こう！
Let's compete earnestly!
暴れん坊なウチら見る夢に限界はないよ
There's no limit to the dreams that we wild things see!
可能性100%で生まれていれば100%で生きていくぜ
If I was born with 100% potential, I'll live at 100%!
泣いたり笑ったりして色んな人に出会う
I cry, I laugh, and I meet a lot of people,
大事なもの見つけたりなくしたり
finding important things and losing them.
がんがん走っていけたほうが楽しいじゃん
It's more fun if you run at full speed!
あれもしたいこれもしたい
I want to do this and that!
行くぞ 進め ガチンコで行こう！
Let's go, advance, and compete earnestly!
世界に一人の自分のために
For the one and only me in this world,
大好きなことをきっときっと見つけてやれ
I'll surely, surely find what I love most!
恥ずかしがりなウチらする恋はドキドキしている
The love that shy girls like us feel makes our hearts race,
本当の気持ちはなぜかやけに我慢をしている
For some reason, I'm holding back my true feelings.
違うこと言ってたり言われたり
Saying different things and being told different things,
がんがん走っていけたほうが生きているじゃん
running at full speed is really living!
あれも欲しいこれも欲しい
I want that, I want this too!
行くぞ 進め ガチンコで行こう！
Let's go, advance, and compete earnestly!
そうだよ やるなら今しかない
That's right, if I'm going to do it, now's the time!
我慢はできないだからもっともっとしたい
I can't hold back, so I want to do more and more!
泣いたり笑ったりして色んな人に出会う
I cry, I laugh, and I meet a lot of people,
大事なもの見つけたりなくしたり
finding important things and losing them.
がんがん走っていけたほうが楽しいじゃん
It's more fun if you run at full speed!
あれもしたいこれもしたい
I want to do this and that!
行くぞ 進め ガチンコで行こう！
Let's go, advance, and compete earnestly!
世界に一人の自分のために
For the one and only me in this world,
大好きなことをきっときっと見つけてやれ
I'll surely, surely find what I love most!
がんがん走っていけたら世界に一人の自分のために
If I run at full speed, for the one and only me in this world,
ガチンコで行こう！大事なことをきっときっと見つけてやれ
Let's compete earnestly! I'll surely, surely find what I love most!
泣いたり笑ったりして色んな人に出会う
I cry, I laugh, and I meet a lot of people...
恋がしたい
I want to fall in love,
愛したい
I want to love.
クリスマスは盛り上げたい
I want to make Christmas exciting!
oh no
今のままでは
if things stay like this,
何も
nothing
hey
変わんない
will change!
大人任せじゃダメ
Relying on adults won't do.
友達集めてね
Gather your friends, okay?
臨時会議
An emergency meeting!
盆暮れ正月バレンタイン
Obon, New Year's, Valentine's,
一人で過ごしたくない
I don't want to spend them alone!
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband,
どこかに目印をつけて
put a mark on yourself somewhere!
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband,
どこかに目印をつけて
put a mark on yourself somewhere!
歩いて
Walk by
ちょうだい
and show yourself!
恋がしたい
I want to fall in love,
愛したい
I want to love.
痛いが痛い
It hurts, it hurts!
クリスマスはもう盛り上げた
I already made Christmas exciting!
痛いが痛い
It hurts, it hurts!
oh no
今のままでは
if things stay like this,
何もない
there's nothing at all!
変わらない
It won't change!
大人任せじゃダメ
Relying on adults won't do.
友達集めてね
Gather your friends, okay?
臨時会議
An emergency meeting!
盆暮れ正月バレンタイン
Obon, New Year's, Valentine's,
一人で過ごしたくない
I don't want to spend them alone!
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband,
どっかに目印をつけて
put a mark on yourself somewhere!
歩いてちょうだい
Walk by and show yourself!
恋がしたい
I want to fall in love,
愛したい
I want to love.
悔しいかない
It's so frustrating!
恋するより気楽だし
It's much more carefree than falling in love,
oh no そんなことでは
oh no, with something like that,
今より最悪
it's worse than right now!
明日からでは遅い
Starting tomorrow is too slow!
たったの今からね
It should begin right from this moment!
さあ始めよう
Now, let's begin!
身長体重血液型 こだわりとかあったけど
Height, weight, blood type, I used to be picky about those,
素敵な未来のだんな様
my wonderful future husband,
結局好きになれば好き
if I end up loving him, then he's the one!
明日からでは遅い
Starting tomorrow is too slow!
たったの今からね
It should begin right from this moment!
さあ始めよう
Now, let's begin!
身長体重血液型 こだわりとかあったけど
Height, weight, blood type, I used to be picky about those,
素敵な未来のだんな様
my wonderful future husband,
結局好きになれば好き
if I end up loving him, then he's the one!
盆暮れ正月バレンタイン
Obon, New Year's, Valentine's,
一人で過ごしたくない
I don't want to spend them alone!
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband,
どっかに目印をつけて
put a mark on yourself somewhere!
歩いてちょうだい
Walk by and show yourself!
期待されると
When people expected things of me,
喜びよりも憂鬱になった
I felt more melancholy than joy.
愛されると
When I was loved,
喜びよりも疑っていた
I felt more doubt than happiness.
そんな私の名前は
The person I am still lives
あの時をまだ生きている
in that moment.
進んだ夢は
The dreams I've chased
まるで誰かの記憶のように
feel like someone else's memories.
おしえて
Tell me why.
私を置いて
Leave me behind as
時代は去っていく
time passes on.
ねえ振り返って
Won't you look back?
気付いてよかまってもらって
Notice me, care about me.
迷路の前ただ誰かを待って
Waiting in front of a maze,
踏み出せず出口は見つかるはずもない
and taking no step forward, no way out will ever appear.
幸せを拒んでいた
I turned away from happiness.
悔しい時ほど
When I was frustrated,
平気だよと笑ってみせた
I pretended to be fine and smiled.
息が切れると
When I was out of breath,
平気だよと冷静に見せた
I kept calm and acted like it didn't hurt.
そんな事していつしか
Doing those things, over time,
違う私が支配した
a different "me" took control.
自分を欺けば
I thought if I could deceive myself,
強くなれるような気がした
I'd grow stronger.
誰も知らずに
If the end came without anyone knowing,
終わりが来たとしても
then even putting on a brave face
もう強がりも意味がないそんな世界
would be pointless in a world like that.
違う何かでやり直せるとして
If I could start over as someone else,
それでもあまのじゃくな私を選ぶのだろう
I'd still choose my contrary self.
私を置いて
Leave me behind as
季節は流れしていく
seasons flow onward,
昨日より強くなれたなら
if only I could become stronger than yesterday,
泣きながら
crying while still moving forward.
全部全部今日も見ない
All, all, I won't look at them today either,
話せない日だってブルーじゃない
even on days we can't talk, I'm not blue.
最低先輩と
Being this close with the worst upperclassman,
すごく仲がいいのも
getting along so well...
全部全部今日も見ない
All, all, I won't look at them today either,
話せない日だってブルーじゃない
even on days we can't talk, I'm not blue.
君の顔も覚えない
I won't even remember your face.
遊園地に誘われても
Even if you invite me to an amusement park,
制服違いで一緒だから
we'd be in different uniforms together,
一度くらい行けても
so even if we could go just once,
優しくされたり
if you're kind to me
神様褒められたり
or if God praises me,
恋愛今日そうあたり
romance might hit me today.
遠く離れたり
Drifting far apart,
喧嘩とかしちゃったり
or getting into a fight,
優しくされたり
if you're kind to me
神様褒められたり
or if God praises me,
優しくされたり
if you're kind to me
神様褒められたり
or if God praises me,
勉強今日そうあたり
studying might hit me today.
全部全部今日も見ない
All, all, I won't look at them today either,
話せない日だってブルーじゃない
even on days we can't talk, I'm not blue.
君の顔も覚えない
I won't even remember your face.
守ってくれてても
Even if you protect me,
全部全部今日見ない
I won't look at it all today either.
もうすぐ引っ越しするんでしょ
You're moving away soon, right?
これ以上優しくしないで
Don't be any kinder to me than this.
嘘泣きしてあげるから
I'll cry fake tears for you.
Ten-chan!
Bye-bye, girls! Well, that was our...
next big part, the first half or so, of the nice, super awesome special guest segment!
The first song was "Kachinko de Iko". It was performed with PiPla and...
and I want to hear you in the chat! Ahh! Ahh!
That's right, yeah. I managed to finally get I'm a Bat for a performance,
and if anyone would make that happen, you'd know it would be number one teammate Takanashi Kiara, right? Of course it was!
I miss her already.
That song was from Buono!, which is a special unit that came together with two members of, uh, two members from Berryz Kobo, and one from ℃-ute.
Yes. They're so awesome, they're so legendary.
Speaking of Berryz Kobo, after that came "Watashi no Mirai no Danna-sama" with special guest Ina! Ina, Ina, Ina! And Nerissa, the super tall one.
That song is one of my favorite songs from Berryz Kobo, and it's about finding the ideal "husbandundo" (husbandundo, Danna-sama is husband).
The height difference from Ina and Nerissa was kind of crazy in that one. Is what they call a moe gap? I think so.
And then we had "Amanojaku" performed by our guest Ina again, and Fuwa and Mococo, together they are Fuwamoco!
Yeah. It's from another one of my favorite idol groups from Hello! Project, called S/mileage. They were made up of four members, but they quickly had some graduations and added many members, and they have since been renamed to Angerme.
Amanojaku was actually their debut song. So it's super sweet and innocent, fitting these members that we have, right? I agree too.
Next up is another song, but let's head over to a new place. That one up there. We shall go in there, okay? Will you follow me? Okay, I'll take the, the way around, I won't go directly, I'll go there, okay? Follow me! Bye-bye!
あくびが一つ出ちゃうほど つまらない午後になったな
I let out a yawn, it has become such a dull afternoon.
ナンパとかしないでくれるかな しらけちゃう
I wonder if you won't hit on me or anything, it's a killjoy.
しばらくはゲンキなキャラで なんとなく生きてきたけど 気付けば色気も出てきているみたい
For a while I lived as a cheerful character somehow, but before I knew it, it seems sexiness is coming out too.
ああ なんだなんだろう私 夕暮れになる度 泣きたい気持ちになる ああ oh baby
Ah, what on earth am I? Every time it gets to dusk, I feel like crying, ah oh baby.
夢は全部真剣だから 大人になる条件を 教えてほしい だけどなんだか面倒臭い
My dreams are all serious, so I want you to tell me the conditions to become an adult, but somehow it's troublesome.
そのうちテレビを買い替えないといけないね
Before long, I gotta replace the TV, huh.
なんちゃって恋愛をしたところで寂しくなるだけ それなのにぬくもりを感じたい
Even if I have a fake romance, I just get lonely. Even so, I want to feel warmth.
なんちゃって良い奴を演じてもむなしくなるだけ それなのに適当に愛想笑い
Even if I act like a nice guy, I just feel empty. Even so, I give a casual polite smile.
ハンバーガーかじりながら街行く人を眺めてた
Biting into a hamburger, I gazed at people walking in the town.
本当に笑ってる子なんているのかな ヘッドフォンから流れてるお気に入りの曲が繰り返し この歌詞は私のこと歌ってる
I wonder if there are really kids smiling. My favorite song playing from headphones repeats over and over. These lyrics are singing about me.
ああ なんだなんだろう私 素直に甘えられない お母さんに電話がしたい ああ oh baby 明日は何をするの私
Ah, what on earth am I? I can't honestly rely on anyone, I want to call Mom. Ah oh baby, what will I do tomorrow, me?
何を求めるのか oh yeah
What am I searching for, oh yeah.
愛が足りない だけど意味なくぐだりしない
Love is not enough, but I won't slack off pointlessly.
あくびがひとつ出ちゃうほど
A yawn escapes me so...
つまらない午後になったな
It's become such a boring afternoon.
ナンパとかしないでくれるかな
Won't you hit on me or something?
しらけちゃう
I'll just lose interest.
しばらくはゲンキなキャラで
For a while, playing a cheerful character,
なんとなく生きてきたけど
I've been living somewhat naturally.
気付けば色気も出てきているみたい
Now I notice charm coming out too.
ああ なんてなんだろう 私 夕方になる度
Ah, why is it every time evening comes,
泣きたい気持ちになる
I feel like crying?
ああ Oh baby 夢は全部本気だから
Ah, Oh baby, because my dreams are serious,
大人になる条件を教えてほしい
I want you to tell me what it takes to be an adult.
だけど なんだか面倒くさい
However, somehow it's a hassle.
そのうちテレビを買い換えわないといけないね
Before long I'll have to replace my TV.
なんちゃって恋愛をしたところで
Even if I have a fake romance,
寂しくなるだけ
I just end up feeling lonely.
それなのにぬくもりを感じたくなる
Even so, I want to feel warmth.
なんちゃって良い奴を演じても
Even if I act like a good person,
虚しくなるだけ
I just end up feeling empty.
それなのに適当に愛想笑い
Even so, I give a half-hearted smile.
ハンバーガーかじりながら
While biting into a hamburger,
街行く人を眺めてた
I was watching the people walking down the street.
本当に笑ってる子なんているのかな
I wonder if there are any kids who are truly smiling.
ヘッドフォンから流れている お気に入りの曲が繰り返し
The favorite song flowing from my headphones repeats.
この歌詞は私のこと歌ってる
These lyrics are singing about me.
ああ なんてなんだろう 私
Ah, why is it, me?
素直に甘えられない
I can't honestly rely on others.
お母さんに電話がしたい
I want to call my mom.
ああ Oh baby
Ah, Oh baby.
明日は何をするの 私
What will I do tomorrow?
何を求めてるの Oh yeah
What am I searching for? Oh yeah.
愛が足りない だけど
I lack love, but...
意味なくぐれたりしないだって
I won't go astray without reason, because
そんなの勿体ない you know?
that would be such a waste, you know?
愛したい
I want to love.
なんちゃって恋愛を繰り返す 女の子の気持ち
Repeating fake romance, a girl's feelings
誰にでも分かっちゃうわ 女の子なら
anyone would understand if they're a girl.
なんちゃって色々と言うけれど 輝きたいだけ
Saying all sorts of fake things, I just want to shine.
私でもなれるかしら 本物に
Could even I become the real thing?
Independent Girl～独立女子であるために～
[Title: Independent Girl ~For Being an Independent Woman~]
目覚めてよ そんな涙を流させたのは彼なんて
Open your eyes. The one who made you shed those tears is him?
あなたのことを愛していたら きっとひどいことできないはずでしょ
If he loved you, surely he wouldn't do such awful things.
おかしいよ 気づかないうち人に振り回されちゃって
It's strange, without realizing it, you get pushed around by others.
服の趣味とか髪の色まで誰かの言いなりになってる
Even your taste in clothes and hair color are at someone else's beck and call.
恋は盲目と言うよ bad medicine みたいなもんだよ
They say love is blind, it's like a bad medicine.
本当の愛はそんな辛くないアイヤ
Real love isn't that painful, a-iya.
independent girl じゃなきゃダメさ a-han
You've got to be an independent girl, a-han.
声を聞かせてよ 誰かのものなんかじゃないんだ 私たち
Let us hear your voice, we aren't anybody's possessions.
independent girl じゃなきゃダメさ a-han
You've got to be an independent girl, a-han.
こっちを向いてよ 自分の生き方くらい自分で決めてみよ
Look this way, decide how to live your own life by yourself.
ニコニコ笑う馬鹿なオンナに成り下がっているあなたなんて
You, stooping to the level of a foolish, grinning woman—
本当のあなたなんかじゃないわ 早く現実に気づいて
that isn't the real you. Hurry up and realize reality.
携帯やたらとチェックされて身動き取れない毎日
Your phone constantly checked, unable to move a muscle every day.
まるで奴隷みたいよ 悲しいっていうなアイヤ
Like a slave, don't say it's sad, a-iya.
independent girl にならなくちゃ a-han
You've got to become an independent girl, a-han.
すぐに取り戻せ 自分で決めた答えはきっと正しい
Regain it immediately, the answer you decided on is surely right.
independent girl にならなくちゃ a-han
You've got to become an independent girl, a-han.
あなたはあなたよ 私たちの未来は自分で切り開くの
You are you, we carve out our own future ourselves.
ニコニコ笑う馬鹿なオンナに成り下がっているあなたなんて
You, stooping to the level of a foolish, grinning woman—
本当のあなたなんかじゃないわ 早く現実に気づいて
that isn't the real you. Hurry up and realize reality.
携帯やたらとチェックされて身動き取れない毎日
Your phone constantly checked, unable to move a muscle every day.
まるで奴隷みたいよ 悲しいっていうなアイヤ
Like a slave, don't say it's sad, a-iya.
independent girl にならなくちゃ a-han
You've got to become an independent girl, a-han.
すぐに取り戻せ 自分で決めた答えはきっと正しい
Regain it immediately, the answer you decided on is surely right.
independent girl にならなくちゃ a-han あなたはあなたよ 私たちの未来は自分で切り開くの
You've got to become an independent girl, a-han. You are you...
目を覚ましてよ
Open your eyes.
そんな涙を流させたのは彼なんて
Those tears you shed are for him?
あなたのことを愛していたら きっとひどいことできないはずでしょう
If he loved you, he wouldn't do those awful things, right?
おかしいよ 気づかないうち人に振り回されちゃって
It's strange, without even noticing, you gave in to other people,
服の趣味とか髪の色まで誰かの言いなりになってる
letting others dictate your taste in clothes and hair color.
恋は盲目って言うよ bad medicineみたいなモンよ
They say love is blind, like a bad medicine.
本当の愛はそんな辛くないからアイヤ
Real love isn't that painful, a-ha!
independent girlじゃなきゃダメさa-han
If you're not an independent girl, it's bad, uh-huh!
声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice!
誰ものものなんかじゃないんだよ私たち
We aren't anyone's possessions.
independent girlじゃなきゃダメさa-han こっちを向いてよ
If you're not an independent girl, it's bad, uh-huh! Look this way!
自分の生き方くらい自分で決めてみなよ
At least decide how you want to live your own life!
切り開くの...
Opening up...
independent
girlじゃなきゃダメさa-han
girl, if you're not, it's bad, uh-huh!
声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice!
誰ものものなんかじゃないんだよ
We aren't anyone's possessions!
私たち independent
We are independent
girlじゃなきゃダメさa-han
girls, if we're not, it's bad, uh-huh!
こっちを向いてよ
Look this way!
自分の生き方くらい自分で
At least decide how you live your own life
breathing on your own terms,
決めてみなよ
decide for yourself!
Ee... I got the memory! Yattsu zo!
Uh... I got the memory! Let's go!
Hello!
私たち independent girls! Yes! We're the independent girls! Joshi! Yes, let's go!
We're independent girls! Yes! We're the independent girls! Girls! Yes, let's go!
Okay, let me please let me hear some introductions. How about we start with my senpai? My... What?
Okay, please let me hear some introductions. How about we start with my senpai? My... What?
I'm your senpai by one stream! It's like we're twins, you know? Who's born first? True, that's a good point. Okay, I guess that would be me.
Me next song! It's me, Mori Calliope. If you hold live, English is rapping, reaper, singer, songwriter. Hello everybody! Uh, if you don't know me, now you do. Who's next?
Me next song! It's me, Mori Calliope. Hololive English's rapping reaper, singer, songwriter. Hello everybody! Uh, if you don't know me, now you do. Who's next?
Next kouhai, cucumber.
Okay then! Hi guys, it's IRyS from Hololive English Promise. You say it's enough to let me here to bring hope to this world...
Oh, if you say so of all of us! Kohaires! Welcome! Welcome, girls!
We have just performed Independent Girl (Dokuritsu Joshi de aru tameni) by Buono! It's a long title! Dokuritsu Joshi!
We have just performed Independent Girl (Dokuritsu Joshi de Aru Tame ni) by Buono! It's a long title! Dokuritsu Joshi!
And we're now inside ballad room, or the building that was behind previously. It's like a planetarium! Pretty, right? You can move in here with me if you want to.
Sure. I kind of want to go for a walk outside. Steaptons? Maybe not, because don't we want to be independent girls? Why would we live together? That's true.
Speaking of that, come back independent lady! You want to be an independent girl, I don't know.
I want to ask you girls something. What makes you such an independent girl?
Oh, that's such a great cue! I didn't have time to prepare for this at all.
For Mori, I always was playing alone by myself at the playground. But beyond that, I... Yeah, yeah. I have no friends.
Oh, now too. You go to the playground? You can see the park outside. It's so lovely.
No, for me, the main reason I think I'm independent an independent girl is because I do a lot of music stuff on my own, like I write my own songs and stuff like that. And I do a lot of things myself, so I feel like that's something an independent person has to do.
I count that. Little bit of a lone wolf. Yeah, what about you? How are you independent?
Yeah, I would say, well, it's many things, like for example, like, oh, ever since last year, I own a home! And that might make some people cry right now, it's too depressing. But yeah, also having my own babies, aka my cats.
But anyway, I want to hear what independent versus independent, or is she not very independent at all?
Independent? Ararara! Independent? What makes you not independent, then?
Maybe we can fix it. I... I can't open water...
I can open water bottles by myself, if I try really hard! I can wake up with with multiple alarms! I... I can... I can...
Do stuff!
Does it- Has it turned out we sang this song to IRyS?
You have to be an independent girl teaching her a lesson.
I am so independent! I did not have my manager feed me medicine right before that!
I saw that! I heard that! Hey, Kiara, can you put it right into-
I saw that! I heard that! Hey, Kiara, can you put it right into—
We believe you. That's a lie.
Oh my god. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
So anyway, we will continue teaching her some lessons about independence, right?
She can't be independent for now though, so we're gonna go for a walk in a...
...park together.
Take me to the park! Take me to the park, girl!
Okay, I'll teach you the ways.
Thanks for the invite, Kiara! It was fun!
Bye-bye! Have fun with it!
All right, come on, IRyS, we're gonna go for a walk now. Yeah, oh my god.
Yeah. Well, that was independent girls right there. But going on, moving on, I think I'll put my microphone away...
...so I can have a little bit more freedom with my arms and maybe I'll attach some LEDs to this outfit. Got switch some batteries. So, I'll see you in a minute!
思い出したくない
I don't want to remember
恋もしてきたわ
I've been in love too
若気の至りって奴ね
Being young and foolish
それでも後悔は
But having no regrets
しないのが私流
Is my way of doing things
自分が生きてきた道だから
Because this is the path I've lived through
嘘をついてまでして
Even telling lies just to
体裁取繕って
Keep up appearances
逆に疲れないんだろうか
Don't you get tired of that?
夢が 夢が 夢が かすむ
My dreams, my dreams, my dreams are fading
このまま引き下がれない
I won't back down now
次の扉開けば
When the next door opens,
未来が見える ほら
The future comes into view, see?
シンプルなkissくらいじゃ
A simple kiss won't suffice
ごまかされないよ
I won't be fooled by that
次のチャンス掴めば
If I grab the next chance,
更なるチャンス ほら
Another chance awaits, see?
複雑な青春の 糸をほぐすように
Like untangling the threads of a complicated youth
Love take it all
好きでもないのに
Even when I didn't love them
ただなんとなく 付き合ったりもしたけど
Just going out with them somehow
起き上がれない程 高熱出した日も
Even on days with a fever so high I couldn't get up
会いに行きたい 恋もしたよ
I was in love enough to go see you
時が 時が 時が 刻む
Time, time, time ticks on
昨日にはもう戻れない
I can never return to yesterday
次の扉開けば
When the next door opens,
未来が見える ほら
The future comes into view, see?
映画に出てきそうな 台詞じゃ足りない
Lines straight out of a movie aren't enough
次のチャンス掴めば
If I grab the next chance,
更なるチャンス ほら
Another chance awaits, see?
誰もまだ通っていない 新たなる扉
A brand new door that no one has crossed yet
Love take it all
次の扉開けば
When the next door opens,
未来が見える ほら
The future comes into view, see?
シンプルなkissくらいじゃ
A simple kiss won't suffice
ごまかされないよ
I won't be fooled by that
次のチャンス掴めば
If I grab the next chance,
更なるチャンス ほら
Another chance awaits, see?
複雑な青春の 糸をほぐすように
Like untangling the threads of a complicated youth
Love take it all
思い出したくない 恋もして来たわ
I didn't even want to remember, but I've had my share of love
若気の至りってやつね
That's just youthful folly, right?
それでも後悔はしないのが私流
Even so, my style is to have no regrets.
Love take it all
最新の洋服に着替えた
I changed into the latest fashion
こんな日はなんだか
On a day like this, somehow
街に出て歩きたい
I want to go out and walk the town
風吹いて 前髪乱れても
The wind blows, messing up my bangs
それでもまあいいよね
Even so, it's alright, isn't it?
私に変りはない
There's no change in me
寂しい夜に繋がる
Connected to lonely nights
秘密の場所がある
There's a secret place
WOO YEAH
そう 私たちの絆
Yeah, our bond
胸張って!生きていけるんですって
Standing tall, we can live on!
輝け!夢があるから
Shine! Because we have dreams
大人にならなくちゃね
We've gotta grow up
わがまましちゃって反省
Being selfish and reflecting on it
輝け!今日の私よ
Shine! Today's me
胸張って!未来の私も
Standing tall! Even my future self
後悔しないように
Won't have any regrets
信じて歩こう
Walking my stage believing
MY STAGE
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
最近ね ひらめきが冴えてる
Lately, my inspirations are sharp
新しい友情に
To new friendships
出会えたりもしたし
Meeting new friends and stuff
いつも行く あの店のあいつは
The guys in that store we always go to
確かにかっこいいよね
They're certainly cool
話しかけちゃおうかな
Maybe I should talk to him
どっちも譲りあわずに
Without either of us giving in
ケンカになったわ
We fought
WOO YEAH
どうやって謝ろうかな???
How am I gonna apologize?
輝け!愛があるから
Shine! Because we have love
そうやって 許しあえるんですって
So we can forgive one another
ネガティブ 言ってても
Even if you say negative things
良いことなんてないし
It's not good
輝け!今日の地球も
Shine! Today's earth as well
胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Standing tall! Let's hold hands
家族の言葉を
The words of my family
信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
青春コレクション
Seishun Collection
最近ね ひらめきが冴えてる
Lately, my inspirations are sharp
新しい友情に 出会えたりもしたし
Meeting new friends and stuff
いつも行く あの店のあいつは
The guys in that store we always go to
確かに かっこいいよね
They're certainly cool
いつもの行こう あの店のあいつは
The guy at that shop we always go to
確かに かっこいいよね
He's definitely cool
確かに かっこいいよね 話しかけちゃおうかな
He's definitely cool, maybe I should talk to him
どっちも譲りあわずに ケンカになったわ
Without either of us giving in, we fought
WOO YEAH どうやって謝ろうかな
Woo yeah, how am I gonna apologize?
輝け!愛があるから
Shine! Because we have love
そうやって 許しあえるんですって
So we can forgive one another
ネガティブ 言ってても 良いことなんてないし
Even if you say negative things, it's not good
輝け!今日の地球も 胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Shine! Today's earth too, standing tall, let's hold hands
家族の言葉を 信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing in the words of my family
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
どっちも譲りあわずに ケンカになったわ
Without either of us giving in, we fought
WOO YEAH どうやって謝ろうかな
Woo yeah, how am I gonna apologize?
輝け!愛があるから
Shine! Because we have love
そうやって 許しあえるんですって
So we can forgive one another
ネガティブ 言ってても 良いことなんてないし
Even if you say negative things, it's not good
輝け!今日の地球も 胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Shine! Today's earth too, standing tall, let's hold hands
家族の言葉を 信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing in the words of my family
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
輝け!愛があるから
Shine! Because we have love
そうやって 許しあえるんですって
So we can forgive one another
ネガティブ 言ってても 良いことなんてないし
Even if you say negative things, it's not good
輝け!今日の地球も 胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Shine! Today's earth too, standing tall, let's hold hands
家族の言葉を 信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing in the words of my family
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
輝け!今日の地球も
Shine! Today's earth too
胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Standing tall! Let's hold hands
家族の言葉を 信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing in the words of my family
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
輝け!今日の地球も
Shine! Today's earth too
胸張って!手を取り合おうよ
Standing tall! Let's hold hands
家族の言葉を 信じて歩こう MY STAGE
Walking my stage believing in the words of my family
OH YEAH 青春コレクション
Oh yeah, Seishun Collection
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Gigi Murin!
Cecilia Immergreen!
Raora Panthera!
And we are Justice!
Justice! Just like that! Get get dance!
Okay, girls. You girls will have to work a little bit more on your sync, but besides that, beautiful.
So, we just had a beautiful song, a little bit of a performance together. It was like your first time in like 3D cardboard.
I was so happy to be 2D! I am so happy to be 2D!
And we I think Ha-dan's sing was a bit flat.
And I think Ha-dan's singing was a bit flat.
Oh, it was beautiful. Sometimes you got to get on the floor. You already have that down.
So, every time Season Collection from Morning Musume. And as you noticed, in the beginning of the song, you know, we had some messages lying there that were written by these cutie pututies. So, let's have a little bit of a look at those messages, shall we?
So, we sang "Seishun Collection" from Morning Musume. And as you noticed, in the beginning of the song, you know, we had some messages lying there that were written by these cutie patooties. So, let's have a little bit of a look at those messages, shall we?
I'm going to get my... Let's look, let's look.
I'm going to get mine... Let's look, let's look.
Okay, so I'll start with introducing my message. Um, mine's a bit more generic or something. I don't know, this is not really towards anybody. But, it says, 'Love, unconditionally. Thanks for coming! By Wawa.'
And now, please uh, in your usual order, tell me about your message and what you wrote for me.
Ah, I wrote 'Love you, to Kiwawa'.
And then there's little flowers around it to represent us as Justice, because yeah, we love everyone, yeah. Wow, I'm so happy we could be part of your song. Thank you.
Mine says, 'Otsukare Kiwawa!! Because you work so hard, and I'm happy to be here, and L-O-V-E! I love you too!'
And who else? What else do we have?
I wrote mine in German. I wrote, 'Vielen Dank! Kiara-Senpai! Hab dich lieb!'
And last but not least... I wrote mine, Ti Amo for you! Ti Amo Kiara!! Thank you for being an amazing Senpai! By Raora Panthera.
And last but not least... I wrote mine—Ti amo for you! "Ti amo Kiara!! Thank you for being an amazing Senpai!" by Raora Panthera.
I'm so happy that we... you know, I took your first time! Thank you for taking my first time! Yes, all right. On-screen stream. It was so much fun! And with that, unfortunately, I have to already send you out because we got some stuff to do.
Thank you Justice so much for coming! Thank you Kiara! Next time in 3D! Bye bye! Bye bye! Bye bye!
It's turning night. How romantic. Well, we are in the home stretch now, so stay with me until the very end.
GO! GO! FIGHT!
ひとつ ふたつ 大きく回せ
One, two, spin them around big
みっつ よっつ さぁ行こう (GO! GO! FIGHT!)
Three, four, let's go (GO! GO! FIGHT!)
LALALA LALALA
愛の歌声が 聞こえてくるから
Because the voice of love songs can be heard
恋するだけなら なんとかなるけど
Just falling in love is manageable somehow, but
愛するとなるとね
when it comes to truly loving someone,
勇気も必要 それより相手よね
you need courage, and even more than that, the other person.
気づけば夏だしそのうち冬だし
Before you know it, it's summer, then soon winter,
なんだか切ないな
somehow it feels a bit poignant.
結局姉貴とランチバイキング
In the end, lunch buffet with big sis,
友達みんな彼氏といちゃいちゃ
all my friends getting cozy with their boyfriends.
くっ付いたり別れたり (軽くね?)
Getting together and breaking up (casually, right?)
本当の恋愛はそんな簡単じゃ見つからないはずさ
True romance shouldn't be that easy to find.
未来は自分の手の中さ 胸を張って YEAH!
The future is in your own hands, stand proud YEAH!
弱気で後ろ向きな私 簡単にには負けない
A timid and backward-looking me won't give up easily.
夢見てだけじゃ夢は叶わない
Just dreaming won't make dreams come true.
通学通勤毎日着る服 (選ぶだけで頭使うわ)
Clothes worn every day for school or work (just choosing them makes my brain hurt)
身長伸びるのすっかり止まって体重増えるのに
My height has completely stopped growing, but my weight keeps increasing,
お菓子はやめてもアイス食べちゃう
even if I quit snacks, I end up eating ice cream.
先生ぼやいてた (大人にはわかんないーだろな)
The teacher was grumbling (grown-ups probably don't understand)
GO!GO! FIGHT! GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT! GO! GO! FIGHT!
ひとつ ふたつ 大きく回せ
One, two, swing them wide,
三つ 四つ さあ行こう
three, four, let's go!
GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT!
LALALA LALALA 愛の歌声が 聞こえてくるから
LALALA LALALA, I can hear the song of love
恋するだけなら何とかなるけど
Just falling in love is easy enough,
愛するとなるとね 勇気も必要 それより相手ね
but loving someone takes courage, and the right partner.
気づけば夏だしそのうち冬だし なんだか切ないな
Before you know it, summer and winter pass, feeling bittersweet.
結局姉貴とランチバイキング
Ultimately having a lunch buffet with my sister,
友達みんな彼といちゃいちゃ くっ付いたり別れたり
friends all with their boyfriends, dating and breaking up
本当の恋愛はそんな簡単じゃ見つからないはずよ
True romance isn't something you find that easily.
未来は自分の手の中さ 胸を張って YEAH!
The future is in your own hands, hold your head high, YEAH!
弱気で後ろ向きな私 簡単には負けない
As timid and backward-looking as I am, I won't lose easily.
夢見てるだけじゃ夢は叶わない 分かっているけどね
Just dreaming won't make dreams come true, I know that, but...
通勤通学毎日着る服 (選ぶだけで頭使うわ)
Clothes I wear to school every day (takes brainpower to choose)
身長伸びるのはすっかり止まって体重増えるのに
My height stopped growing, yet my weight keeps going up,
お菓子はやめてもアイス食べちゃう 先生ぼやいていた
even if I quit snacks, I eat ice cream, as the teacher grumbled.
大人にはわかんないんだろうな
Adults probably don't understand.
そういう部分言っとかなきゃ損をしていけば
If you don't speak up about those parts, you'll lose out;
誰にも負けない楽しさで 飛び立つから
with a fun that loses to no one, I'll take flight.
悔しさり 鼻水まじりの涙とか 流しちゃえばいいじゃん
If frustration or snot-mixed tears come out, just let them flow.
GO!GO! FIGHT! GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT! GO! GO! FIGHT!
未来は自分の手の中さ 胸を張って YEAH!
The future is in your own hands, hold your head high, YEAH!
弱気で後ろ向きな私 簡単には負けない
As timid and backward-looking as I am, I won't lose easily.
ひとつ ふたつ 大きく回せ 三つ 四つ さあ行こう
One, two, swing them wide, three, four, let's go!
GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT!
LALALA LALALA 愛の歌声が 聞こえてくるから
LALALA LALALA, I can hear the song of love
GO!GO!GO!GO! FIGHT! GO!GO!GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! GO! GO! FIGHT! GO! GO! GO! GO! FIGHT!
未来は自分の手の中さ 胸を張って YEAH!
The future is in your own hands, hold your head high, YEAH!
弱気で後ろ向きな私 簡単には負けない
As timid and backward-looking as I am, I won't lose easily.
夢見てるだけじゃ夢は叶わない 分かっているけどね
Just dreaming won't make dreams come true, I know that, but...
通勤通学毎日着る服 (選ぶだけで頭使うわ)
Clothes I wear to school every day (takes brainpower to choose)
身長伸びるのはすっかり止まって体重増えるのに
My height stopped growing, yet my weight keeps going up,
お菓子はやめてもアイス食べちゃう 先生ぼやいていた
even if I quit snacks, I eat ice cream, as the teacher grumbled.
大人にはわかんないんだろうな
Adults probably don't understand.
そういう部分言っとかなきゃ損をしていけば
If you don't speak up about those parts, you'll lose out;
誰にも負けない楽しさで 飛び立つから
with a fun that loses to no one, I'll take flight.
悔しさり 鼻水まじりの涙とか 流しちゃえばいいじゃん
If frustration or snot-mixed tears come out, just let them flow.
GO!GO! FIGHT! GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT! GO! GO! FIGHT!
未来は自分の手の中さ 胸を張って YEAH!
The future is in your own hands, hold your head high, YEAH!
弱気で後ろ向きな私 簡単には負けない
As timid and backward-looking as I am, I won't lose easily.
ひとつ ふたつ 大きく回せ 三つ 四つ さあ行こう
One, two, swing them wide, three, four, let's go!
GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! FIGHT!
LALALA LALALA 愛の歌声が 聞こえてくるから
LALALA LALALA, I can hear the song of love
GO!GO!GO!GO! FIGHT! GO!GO!GO!GO! FIGHT!
GO! GO! GO! GO! FIGHT! GO! GO! GO! GO! FIGHT!
oh ~ it's simple
you gotta do it like
mmm ~
okay, hey ~
i been out of luck
i been stayin' up
praying for anyone to hear
hear the beating drums of my heart give up
i don't know what to do
feel the rhythm, call me on my bluff
can't die no not this way
hopeless girl, haven't i had enough?
n-no-n-no cause i'm a -
shinin' diamond
from nothin to brilliant
oh my, oh i do it casually
levelin' me up
with a shade of violet
tell you my secret
how i
put that lipstick on me
oh a new improved girl, my - perfume, that's what i need, what i need
got that perfume on ~
got that perfume fume-fume on me
got that per-per fume-fume on you
got that perfume on me, on me
i never could define what i could be so i
went on a broken dreamer
uh, puttin' every piece of me back, i'm free
spent so much time just waiting, crying
why
but would you be born if you weren't meant for somethin' greater, baby?
bye sixteen, these years have flown by really
shinin' diamond
from nothin to brilliant
oh my, oh i do it casually
levelin' me up
with a shade of violet
tell you my secret
how i
put that lipstick on me
Oh, a new improved girl, my
Perfume, that's what I need, what I need
Got that perfume on~
I-I-I still feel those
Sinking thoughts, reckless emotions
I-I-I know there's no
Closed door that I can't open
Girl, girl, girls so perfect
Don't don't don't don't doubt it
On me
Put that lipstick on me, stick on me
Oh, a new improved girl, my
Perfume, that's what I need, what I need
Got that perfume on~
Got that perfume fume-fume on me
Got that per-per fume-fume on you
Got that perfume on me, on me
Yippi! And that was my new song.
But before that, before we go into that, I shall explain.
Before the new song, we had one of my favorite songs from my favorite idol group, BEYOOOOONDS.
Rival, which, you know...
That had a really awesome formation, right? It was so fun with like turning around in like different timings and everything.
Really difficult, but really fun, and I think it will look beautiful to you guys, I hope so.
Well, besides that, another song with many members...
Was my new song, Perfume!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! It will be released today.
And the jacket is here, ta-da! It's kind of like...
I wanted it to be like this so it doesn't give away any hint of anime or so, it's just a perfume.
I wonder what smell it is.
Here, smell my armpits.
Then you will find out. Stinky!
Okay, well, that's Perfume, yeah.
And the music video will also come out after this, the premiere.
You may have already seen that it's up, it's about to begin anytime soon, so be ready for it.
It's going to be really beautiful again, with different new 3D outfits.
Maybe perhaps one that I designed as well.
And maybe one that Rao-da designed.
Yeah, that's right, giving away all the secrets already now.
Okay, well, I hope you really enjoyed it. It was really tough.
Perfume practice, I practiced so much on it, and if you maybe noticed, I had even more backup dancers than last time.
Last time was four, and that was the fifth one, was I?
And now it's six, and then the seventh one.
So I wanted things to look even more complicated and more interesting, I hope I managed to do that.
And that was the only song today that is not HoloPro.
And even though probably usually it makes more sense for me to end it on my new original song...
Since this is all HoloPro themed, we will still end it with one more song.
かってなイメージ 決めつけないで
Don't just make up arbitrary images
核心を見せてよ get it on
Look at what's inside, get it on
そうでも私は 噂をされても
Even if people talk about me behind my back,
そんなの気にせず on my way
I won't mind it and go on my way
踊りましょう 止まらないわ
Let's dance, we're not stopping
踊りましょう 忘れるまで
Let's dance, until we forget
言葉で認めちゃって 心の中じゃダメダメ
Admitting it in words, but inside your heart saying no no
よくあることじゃないか everyone
Isn't that a common thing, everyone?
こんなに努力したって すぐには出ない 結果に
Why am I so annoyed at not seeing results
ムカついているの なぜだろう
Right away despite putting in so much effort?
bye bye bye ! 明るく生きろ 楽しもう
Bye bye bye! Live cheerfully, enjoy life
bye bye bye ! 元気にいこうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye bye bye! Go energetically, I'm sure you can do it
bye bye bye ! 自由を描け 膨らまそう
Bye bye bye! Paint freedom, let it grow
勝手なイメージ決め付けないで
Don't just decide on your own image of me,
核心を見てよ get it on
Look at the core, get it on!
そう でも 私は 噂を されても
Even if people talk about me behind my back,
そんなの 気にせず on my way
I won't let it bother me, on my way!
踊りましょ 止まらないわ
Let's dance, it won't stop!
踊りましょ 忘れるまで
Let's dance, until we forget it all!
言葉で 認めちゃって
Even if you say yes with words,
心の中じゃ ダメダメ
deep in your heart, it's a no-no!
良くあること じゃないか everyone
That happens to everyone, right?
こんなに 努力したって
Even when you put in so much effort,
すぐには 出ない 結果に
why does it get so frustrating
ムカついているの なんだろう
when the results don't show right away?
bye bye bye ! 明るく 生きろ 楽しもうね
Bye-bye-bye! Live cheerfully, have fun!
bye bye bye ! 元気に 行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go with high energy!
bye bye bye ! 自由に描け 膨らまそうね
Bye-bye-bye! Freely draw out your dreams!
bye bye bye ! 未来に向かって
Bye-bye-bye! Heading towards the future!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
なんとか 気分を 高めてみたわ
Somehow I tried to lift my mood,
良い雰囲気ね get it on
with a nice atmosphere, get it on!
周りは いつも 色々言うわ
People are always saying various things,
そんなの 気にせず on my way
but I won't mind it, on my way!
踊りましょ 止まらないわ
Let's dance, it won't stop!
踊りましょ 忘れるまで
Let's dance, until we forget it all!
恋したときは なんかさ
When you fall in love, somehow
頭の中が キラキラ
your head sparkles and shines!
輝きながら 全身 beautiful
Shining while feeling beautiful all over!
恋したあとは だって
And after falling in love,
それは それで すっきり
you feel totally refreshed!
明日に向かって 駆け出すよ
Running forward towards tomorrow!
bye bye bye ! 優しく 生きろ 抱きしめろよ
Bye-bye-bye! Live gently, hold me close!
bye bye bye ! 素直に行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go honestly!
bye bye bye ! 胸ときめかせ 夢 抱こうよ
Bye-bye-bye! Let's embrace our dreams!
bye bye bye ! 自分信じて
Bye-bye-bye! Believe in yourself!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
bye bye bye ! 優しく 生きろ 抱きしめろよ
Bye-bye-bye! Live gently, hold me close!
bye bye bye ! 素直に行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go honestly!
bye bye bye ! 胸ときめかせ 夢 抱こうよ
Bye-bye-bye! Let's embrace our dreams!
bye bye bye ! 自分信じて
Bye-bye-bye! Believe in yourself!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
bye bye bye ! 優しく 生きろ 抱きしめろよ
Bye-bye-bye! Live gently, hold me close!
bye bye bye ! 素直に行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go honestly!
bye bye bye ! 胸ときめかせ 夢 抱こうよ
Bye-bye-bye! Let's embrace our dreams!
bye bye bye ! 自分信じて
Bye-bye-bye! Believe in yourself!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
bye bye bye ! 優しく 生きろ 抱きしめろよ
Bye-bye-bye! Live gently, hold me close!
bye bye bye ! 素直に行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go honestly!
bye bye bye ! 胸ときめかせ 夢 抱こうよ
Bye-bye-bye! Let's embrace our dreams!
bye bye bye ! 自分信じて
Bye-bye-bye! Believe in yourself!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
bye bye bye ! 優しく 生きろ 抱きしめろよ
Bye-bye-bye! Live gently, hold me close!
bye bye bye ! 素直に行こうぜ 出来るだろう
Bye-bye-bye! Let's go honestly!
bye bye bye ! 胸ときめかせ 夢 抱こうよ
Bye-bye-bye! Let's embrace our dreams!
bye bye bye ! 自分信じて
Bye-bye-bye! Believe in yourself!
bye bye bye bye bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!